import type { MCQ } from '../../../types'

export const mcqSet4: MCQ[] = [
  {
    "id": 31,
    "question": "What does NLP stand for?",
    "options": [
      "Natural Learning Process",
      "Neural Language Processing",
      "Natural Language Processing",
      "Neural Learning Programming"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 2
  },
  {
    "id": 32,
    "question": "Which of the following techniques is used to reduce words to their base or root forms?",
    "options": [
      "Tokenization",
      "Lemmatization",
      "Stopword Removal",
      "Text Summarization"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 33,
    "question": "Which of the following is NOT a technique used in extractive summarization?",
    "options": [
      "Statistical Approaches",
      "Sequence-to-Sequence Models",
      "Graph-Based Methods",
      "Sentence Scoring"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 34,
    "question": "Which of the following is a graph-based method used in extractive summarization?",
    "options": [
      "BERT",
      "LexRank",
      "LSTM",
      "GPT"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 35,
    "question": "Which of the following is a technique used in abstractive summarization?",
    "options": [
      "TextRank",
      "TF-IDF",
      "Attention Mechanisms",
      "Sentence Scoring"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 2
  },
  {
    "id": 36,
    "question": "Sequence-to-Sequence models commonly used in abstractive summarization include:",
    "options": [
      "BERT and GPT",
      "RNNs and LSTMs",
      "TextRank and LexRank",
      "TF-IDF and LSA"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 37,
    "question": "Which library provides extensive corpora and lexical resources?",
    "options": [
      "NLTK",
      "spaCy",
      "Keras",
      "Theano"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 0
  },
  {
    "id": 38,
    "question": "Which library is recommended for production-grade NLP applications?",
    "options": [
      "NLTK",
      "spaCy",
      "Scikit-learn",
      "SciPy"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 39,
    "question": "Who created the first chatbot, Eliza, and when?",
    "options": [
      "Keneth Colby, 1972",
      "Rollo Carpenter, 1988",
      "Joseph Weisenbaum, 1964-1966",
      "ActiveBuddy Inc., 2001"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 2
  },
  {
    "id": 40,
    "question": "What year was the chatbot SmarterChild developed?",
    "options": [
      "1995",
      "2001",
      "1988",
      "2016"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 1
  }
]
